- Oh, boy, I was afraid of this.
- What?
(Howard:)These instructions
are a pictographic representation...
(Howard:)...of the least imaginative way
to assemble these components.
(Howard:)This right here
is why Sweden has no space program.
(Penny:)- It looked pretty good in the store.
- It is an inefficient design.
(Leonard:)For example,
Penny has a flatscreen TV...
...which means all this space
behind it is wasted.
- We could put her stereo back there.
- And control it how?
(Sheldon:)Run an infrared repeater,
photocell here, emitter here, easy-peasy.
- Good point. How will you cool it?
- Guys, I got this.
- Hang on, Penny.
- How about fans?
(Sheldon:)- Here and here.
- Also inefficient, and might be loud.
How about a liquid cooler?
A little aquarium pump here.
Run some quarter-inch PVC...
(Penny:)Guys, this is actually really simple.
(Howard:)Hold on, honey, men at work.
PVC comes here. Maybe a little
corrugated sheet metal as a radiator here.
(Leonard:)Show me where we put a drip tray,
a sluice and a overflow reservoir?
If water's involved,
we'll ground the crap out of the thing.
(Penny:)Guys, it's hot in here.
I think I'll just take off all my clothes.
(Leonard:)Oh, I've got it.
What if we replaced panels A, B and F and
crossbar H with aircraft-grade aluminum?
(Sheldon:)- Entire thing's one big heat sink.
- Perfect.
Leonard and Sheldon, go to the junkyard
and pick up 6 square meters of aluminum.
- Raj and I will get the oxyacetylene torch.
- Meet in an hour?
(Leonard:)- Done.
- Got it.
(Penny:)Okay, this place does look pretty good.